storyjumper.com 2014-07-02

# StoryJumper: Publish and read children's story books

This Privacy Policy was last updated: Oct. 1, 2009

**StoryJumper, Inc. Privacy Policy**

StoryJumper, Inc. (“StoryJumper” or “we” or “us”) is dedicated to safeguarding the personal information collected online through StoryJumper’s Internet website located at StoryJumper.com and any of its subdomains (collectively, the “Site”) and the services and software on the Site. This Privacy Policy is intended to explain our privacy practices and inform you as to: (1) our privacy practices with respect to children under the age of 13; (2) the types of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") we collect from users of the Site; (3) how Personal Information is collected; (4) how we use Personal Information; (5) the circumstances under which we disclose Personal Information to third parties; (6) how you can access, update or delete any of your Personal Information collected by us; and (7) the processes we have implemented to protect your Personal Information. As we continue to update our website with new and different types of products and services, we may modify our Privacy Policy from time to time. However, we will treat all personal information we collect in accordance with the Privacy Policy in effect at the time the information is collected. This Privacy Policy is a part of our Terms of Service. Any terms that are not defined in this Privacy Policy shall have the meaning given in the StoryJumper Terms of Service.

**Children’s Privacy**

We recognize the need to provide additional privacy protections for younger children who visit our Site. The Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”) requires that we inform parents and legal guardians about how we collect, use, and disclose personal information from children under 13 years of age and that we obtain the consent of parents and guardians in order for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of our Site. **Please be aware that our Children’s Privacy Policy, viewable here www.storyjumper.com/main/coppa, which is hereby incorporated by reference, governs our collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information from children under 13 years of age. **

Where a visitor self-identifies as under 13 years of age during the initial registration process, we collect the child’s birth date, user name, password and parent’s or legal guardian’s e-mail address. We ask the child not to use his or her real name as all or part of the user name. We use the parent’s or legal guardian’s e-mail address solely for the purpose of asking the parent or legal guardian for his or her consent and activating the account on the Site. Any information provided by the child is not used to contact the child unless or until we receive parental or legal guardian consent.  Any Personal Information except the user name of the child that is collected through the initial registration process before receiving the parent’s or legal guardian’s consent will be encrypted and stored on our servers with the key to decrypt the data stored in a cookie on the computer the child is using. The e-mail we send to the parent or legal guardian requesting his or her consent will contain the key to decrypt the child’s Personal Information. In addition, when a parent or legal guardian activates an account on the Site, we may collect additional Personal Information of the parent or legal guardian at that time, including the parent's name, contact information and credit card billing information (including telephone number and mailing address).

**The Information We Collect**

Visitors to the Site may browse stories on the Site without providing any Personal Information. To participate in our basic and premium memberships and to purchase products from us, however, we ask the user to register for an account on the Site and to provide us with certain Personal Information as further described below. 

Where a visitor self-identifies as 13 years and older during the registration process, we will collect a valid e-mail address, birth date, username and password from the user. In the event that the user purchases a premium membership to the Site or orders a product from us (for example, a book), we will collect name, credit card and billing information (including telephone number and billing address), and we may collect additional information such as gender and country of residence. 

We may also request a user name and email address when a user submits a form through our "Contact Us" feature on the Site so that we may respond to the inquiry. We will use the e-mail address submitted through the “Contact Us” feature for the single purpose of responding directly on a one-time basis to a specific inquiry. We also may collect information about you and your use of our Site, services and/or software through your use of our Site, services and/or software.

Additionally, when visitors come to our Site, we automatically collect some non-personally identifiable information about the user’s computer and/or browser, such as type of computer operating system (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS), the visitor's "IP Address", the web browser (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer) being used, information collected through the use of cookies (see below) and information regarding the Internet service provider (collectively, "Computer Information"). 

From time to time, StoryJumper may provide you with the opportunity to participate in online contests. To participate in a contest, a user may be asked to provide certain Personal Information, such as name and email address. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. 

**How We Use and Disclose Information**

We use users’ Personal Information for our internal purposes to enable users to register to use the Site and the services on our Site, enter our online contests, send our online newsletter, inform users of upcoming events and special announcements, contact them to deliver certain products and other tangible goods that they have purchased from us (such as books, t-shirts, stickers, etc.), provide them with notices regarding goods or services that they have purchased or may wish to purchase in the future, provide information they have requested and improve the content and general administration of the Site and our services. 

We use a parent’s or legal guardian's email address to send the parent or legal guardian a message that can be used to activate an account and provide consent for children under 13 years of age to use certain features of our Site and to send the parent or legal guardian communications about the account. 

We also use users’ Computer Information to track how the Site is being used, to improve our Site design, to offer products and services, to personalize our users’ experiences, to save a user’s password in password-protected areas, to enable you to use shopping carts on our Site, and to ensure users are following the Site's Terms of Service. In some cases we may provide your Personal Information to third party vendors and suppliers that we engage to help us provide services to our users. For example, we may engage third parties to process your payments, produce products and other tangible goods that you order from us and/or help us fulfill contests and sending prizes to the winners. In these cases, we require the third party to keep the information secure and confidential and to use it only for the specific services they are performing for us. Additionally, in the event of a merger, consolidation or other corporate reorganization in which StoryJumper participates or a sale of all or substantially all of StoryJumper, Inc.'s stock and/or assets to which this Site relates, we may transfer your personal information to the successor entity or purchaser.

We may disclose Personal Information about our users, as well as Computer Information, when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation or by applicable law, rule or regulation, to verify or enforce compliance with the Terms of Service and any other policies governing our Site, or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site or the services on the Site. We also may disclose Personal Information whenever we believe disclosure is necessary to limit our legal liability; to protect or defend our rights or property; or protect the safety, rights, or property of users of our Site or other third parties. 

**Public Story Content and Public Forums**

If you are under 13, you are prohibited from including any Personal Information in any content, text, files, images, photos, videos, sounds, musical works, works of authorship, and any other materials that you post to the Site, including, without limitation, any content in the products and other tangible goods purchased from us or content that you contribute to other members’ stories posted on the Site (“Your Story Content”) unless and until your parent or legal guardian gives permission. We will contact your parent or legal guardian and ask them to activate an account for you. 

After your parent or legal guardian consents if you are under the age of 13, or, if you are 13 or older, you may choose to disclose information, including Personal Information, about yourself in Your Story Content. We may also offer online forums, blogs, comment sections, virtual communities, message boards and/or user profiles for public view or similar forums on the Site (collectively, “Public Forums”) where you may choose to disclose information, including Personal Information. Any of Your Story Content that is designated by you, or, if you are under 13, your parent or legal guardian, as “public” or “shared” and any information that is disclosed in any Public Forum is public information, and you agree that there is no expectation of privacy or confidentiality with respect to such content and information. Please note that any information that is designated by you, or, if you are under 13, your parent or legal guardian, as “public” or “shared” or posted in a Public Forum can be read, collected, or used by other users of the Site, including, without limitation, used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible, and assume no liability for, any uses or disclosures of Personal Information designated as “public” or “shared” or posted in any Public Forum. 

**Unsubscribing from Newsletters**

We will gather the email addresses of users who sign up for the Site for our newsletter mailing list. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by opting out of reviewing newsletters by the instructions on how to unsubscribe contained in each newsletter or by changing their preferences in their account page. 

**Cookies**

The Site places small text files within the preferences of a user’s computer browser, called “Cookies.” Cookies are pieces of data stored on the user’s hard drive that are a way of storing information about the user. Once you provide Personal Information to the Site, this Personal Information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We may also use small pieces of code (example: “clear.gif") to collect anonymous and aggregate metrics, such as counting the number of page views on the site. These pieces of code may also be used to deliver cookies. 

You may adjust your browser to reject cookies from us or from any other Web site. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for more information. However, many areas of our Site can only be accessed with cookies enabled and you should be aware that disabling cookies would prevent you from accessing some features and/or content on our Site. 

Our Privacy Policy does not cover any use of information that a third party ad server or third party analytics server may collect from you. 

**Links to Third Party Sites**

The Site may provide links to other Web sites or resources over which StoryJumper does not have control ("External Web Sites"). Such links do not constitute an endorsement by StoryJumper of those External Web Sites. You acknowledge that StoryJumper is providing these links to you only as a convenience, and further agree that StoryJumper is not responsible for the content of such External Web Sites. Your use of External Web Sites is subject to the terms of use and privacy policies located on the linked to External Web Sites.

**Accessing, Correcting and/or Deleting Personal** **Information**

Users can access and correct their Personal Information supplied upon registration (except for user name, original e-mail address and date of birth) through your account management page, which can be reached through the following URL: http://www.storyjumper.com/user/account and following the direction on such page. You can also delete any Personal Information that is not a required field specified during the registration process or disable your account through your account management page. To delete your account, however, you will need to contact StoryJumper. Upon your request we will delete your account and your user profile as soon as reasonably possible; provided, however, you should understand that any content, feedback, comments, information and/or any other materials, including, without limitation, Your Story Content, and any Personal Information incorporated into any of the foregoing, that you have posted to the Site that is posted in areas other than your user profile and/or that you have designated as being “public” or “shared” and that StoryJumper and/or other users of the Site have made available in areas on the Site other than your user profile may not be deleted and/or removed and may remain on the Site. Any content, feedback, comments, information and/or any other materials, including, without limitation, Your Story Content, and any Personal Information incorporated into any of the foregoing, that you have posted to the Site that remains in our back-up systems will not be deleted. 

**Security**

We may employ procedural and technological measures that are reasonably designed to help protect your personally identifiable information from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. We may use firewalls and password protection to help prevent unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our privacy policy and/or practices, please contact us at the following e-mail address, address, or telephone number: 

privacycontrol@storyjumper.com

Privacy Manager - StoryJumper

2625 Middlefield Road, #256

Palo Alto, CA 94306-2516

**Effective Date, Updates and Acceptance**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of October 1st 2009\. Your use of the Site and services on the Site is subject to this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. Your use of this Site and/or the services on the Site, shall be deemed your acceptance of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. If so, we will post our updated Privacy Policy on this page and post notice of the change so it is visible when users log-on for the first time after the change is posted. Your continued use of any portion of the Site and/or services on the Site following posting of the updated Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the changes.
